ANS Record Group 1: Administrative, 1853-ongoing
American Numismatic Society
- Series: General correspondence, 1853 - 2099; 133 cubic feet
  - Box 2.4.4 #65 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    O (unsorted).; Odon, Gohl (Numizmatikai Kozlony).; O’Donnell, Hubert.; Oettinger, Julia W.; Oettinger, S.; Official Metropolitan Guide (New York, New York).Ogden, Nelson (Stevens Institute of Technology).; Ogden, Robert C.; Ohsa, Robert M. (So. Manchurian Railway Library).; Oikonomos, G. P. (Director, National Numismatic Museum, Athen, Greece).; Olcott, E. E.; Olcott, Zita.; Olcott, George N. (Columbia University).; Oldenbourg, R.; Olds, Irving S.; Olschki, Leo S.; Omaha (NE) Public Library and Museum.; Oman, Charles W. (President, Royal Numismatic Society).; Ongania, Ferdinand.; Oriental Book Shop.; Ormond, M. Georgia.; Orlowski, Alexander.; Orr, R. B. (Director, Provincial Museum of Toronto).; Orr, Viola Ellen.; Orsi, Paolo (Director, R. Museo Archeologico di Siracusa, Syracuse, Sicily).; Osborn, George (Librarian, Rutgers University).; Osborn, William C.; Otis, Philo.; Overall-Hatswell, D. R.; O’Toole, James.; Owen, William H. (Jr.).; Oxford University Press.
  - Box 2.4.5 #66 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    P (unsorted)
  - Box 2.4.6 #67 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Page, Laura L.; Page, Adeline G.; Paladino, Bruno.; Palesty, N.; Palmer and Serles (Newell attorneys).; Paltsits, Victor H. (NY Public Library).; Pandick Press.; Pani, Alberto.; Pappavangelon, Themistoclou.; Parish, Daniel.; Parent, George W.; Park Museum (Providence, Rhode Island).; Parker, A. G.; Parker, C. C.; Paris, William F.; Partridge, Sidney L.; Parshina, A. (Librarian, ____ University, Saratov, Russia).; Parsons, H. Alexander (Honorary Librarian, British Numismatic Society).; Pasqualini, Mattioli (Ministro della Real Casa, Rome, Italy).; Paterson (NJ) Mayor.; Patten, Katharine (Minneapolis Athenaeum).; Pauli, G. E.; Pazquez-Torne, Luis.; Peace Dollar, 1922.; Peacock, C. D.; Pearson & Crain.; Peirce, Hayford.; Pell, Howland.; Pell, Stephen H. P.; Pell Collection circular.; Pelletier, Octave.; Pennell, Frederick.; Pennisi di Floristella, Salvadore.; Penny, Joseph.; Penton, John A.; Perella, Francesco.; Perkins, Edward N.; Perkins, Seymour.; Perkins, William H.; Pernier, Luigi (R. Museo Archiologico, Florence, Italy).; Perreau, Maurice.; Pershing, John J.; Peters, Richard (Numismatic and Antiquarian Society of Phila.); Peterson, Waldo.; Petsalis, ______.
  - Box 2.4.7 #68 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Pharr, Clyde.; Phillips, Stephen.; Phoenix, Lloyd.; Photo-Gelatine Printing Co.; Piccirioli, Attilio.; Pick, Behrendt (Herzogliches Muenzkabinett, Gotha).; Pietz, Adam.; Pinches, John.; Piper, William C.; Place, P. G. (University of Syracuse).; Platt, Clement.; Platt, Dan F.; Plimpton, Russell A. (Director, Minneapolis Institute of Arts).; R. L. Polk & Co.; Poillon, Arthur.; Poillon, William.; Pond, Preston.; Pond, Shepard.; Postmaster—New York City.; Postmaster—Newark, NJ.; Potter, F. Wayland.; Povenmire, H. M.; J. C. & W. E. Powers Co.
  - Box 2.5.1 #69 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Prato, Leon.; Pratt, Frank.; Pratt, George D.; Prentice, Bernon S.; Preis, H. P.; Press clippings (unsorted).; Price, Henry Brooks.; Pridik, Eugen (Director, Hermitage Numismatic Collection).; Princeton University Library.; Proctor, William.; Proskey, David.; Provincial Museum (Lucknow, India).; Pryer, Charles, 1905-1913.; Pryer, Charles, 1914.; Pryer, Charles, 1915.; Pumpelly, Raphael.; Purdy, F. C.; Putnam, E. (Curator, Richester Municipal Museum).; G. P. Putnam & Son.; Putorti, Nicola (Museo Civico, Reggio Calabria, Italy).
  - Box 2.5.2 #70 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Q (unsorted).; Quagliati, Quintino (Museo Archaeologico, Taranto, Italy).; Quaritch, Bernard.; Quinby, Henry C.; Qvist, Gerda
  - Box 2.5.3 #71 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    R (unsorted).
  - Box 2.5.4 #72 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Rackus, A. M.; Rand McNally Co.; Rane, K. R. (Rane’s Museum, India).; Rand, Charles F.; Rapid Transit Celebration Committee (New York, NY).; Rassegna Numismatica (Rome, Italy).; Ratto, Rodolfo.; Raymond, Wayte.; Read, William (Mrs.).; Reed and Barton.; Regling, Kurt (Kaiser-Friedrich-Museum), 1922-1923.; Reid, Ida M.; Reid, R. L.; Reilly, John (Jr.), 1910-1919.; Reilly, John (Jr.), 1920-; Reilly, John (Jr.).; Reilly, John (Jr.)—death.; Reinach, Theodore.; Reuterdahl, Sigrid (New Jersey College for Women).; Revista Italiana di Numismatica (Milan, Italy).; Revue du Vrai et du Beau.; Reynolds, B. H.; Rhind, J. Massey.; Rhinelander, Philip.
  - Box 2.5.5 #73 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Riba e Hermanos.; Ricci, Ulysses A.; Ricci, Serafino (R. Museo Numimatico e Medagliere Nacionale di Brera, Milan).; Richard Oscar.; Richardson, John.; Richmond, Charles A.; Richter, Gisela M. A.; Rico y Cia, Garcia.; A. Riechmann & Co.; Riley, H. E.; Risdon, F. Ray.; Ritsos, Michel.; Roper, Daniel C. (Commissioner, Internal Revenue, U.S. Treasury Department).; Rivista Italiana di Numismatica (Milan, Italy).; The Robbins Co.; Roberts, Elizabeth M. (Concord Art Association).; Robertson, Robert.; Robinson, Charles A. (Jr.).; Robinson, Duane.; Robinson, Edwin P.; Robson & Adee.; Rochester Numismatic Association.; Roe, Frank.; Rolland, H.; Rogers, Daisy F.; Rogers, Edgar.; Rogers, Norman (American Legion).; Rogers & Krull.; Rollman, Henry.; Roman Bronze Works.; Romania—Consul General.; Romeike, Henry.; Rosenberg, H. Sally.; Ross, Christa A.; Rossi, Angelo J.; Rossi, Fillipo (Medagliere Milanese, Milan, Italy).; Roth, Frederick G. R.; Rothenstein, M.; Rottner, G. H.; Rowe, L. Earle (Director, Rhode Island School of Design); Rowland, M. T.; Ruch, Clarence.; Ruhl & Co.; Rumford Press.; Russell, Walter.
  - Box 2.5.6 #74 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    S (unsorted).
  - Box 2.5.7 #75 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Saltus, J. Sanford, 1892-1908.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1910.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1911.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1912.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1913.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1914.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1915.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1916.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1917.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1918.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1919.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1920.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1921.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1922.; Saltus, J. Sanford, 1922-25.;; Box 2.6.1 #76;; Sailor, R. W. (Cornell Publications Printing Co. / Cayuga Press).; Saint-Gaudens, Augustus (Mrs.).; St. Louis Coin and Stamp Co.; St. Louis Numismatic Society.; St. Louis Public Library.; St. Paul (MN) Public Library.; Salemme, Antonio.; Sambon, Arthur.; P. & P. Santamario. (Rome, Italy).; Santi Anna, ______ (Baron).; Saric, L. W. (Newark Fire Insurance Co.).; Sartiges, ______ (Premier Secretaire d’Ambassade).; Sather Gate Book Shop.; Satterlee, Herbert L.; Saxton, Burton H.; Sawyer, Edward W.; Scaifa, Walter B.; Schaefer, Hans.; Scharff, John M.; Schervee, H. (Schervee Studios).; Schiff, Jacob H.; Schiff, Mortimer L.; Schiapparelli, E. (R. Museo di Antichita, Turin, Italy).; Schlosser, Richard.; Schmahl, Roy C.; Schmidt, Charles R.; Schmidt, Ernst C.; Schmidt, G.; Schmuck, T. K.; Schoenhof Book Co.; Schoetz & Parrhyius.; Schoff, Wilfred H. (Commercial Museum).; Schuler, Hans.; Schulman, J.; Schweitzer, B. (Archaeologisches Institute der Universitaet, Heidelberg).; Scott, John M. (Pennsylvania Society of Sons of the Revolution).; Scott, Walter.; Scott, W. S.; Scoville, Herbert.; Charles Schribner’s Sons.
  - Box 2.6.2 #77 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Seaby, Herbert A. (B. A. Seaby, Ltd).; Seederer-Kohlbusch, Inc.; Seidler, Herbert H.; Serafini, Camillo (Director, Cabinetto Numismatico Vaticano).; Serdy, Michael.; Sesquicentennial International Exhibition Committee, 1926.; Severance, Frank H. (Secretary, Buffalo Historical Society).; Severeano, G.; Shakallis, M. K.; Shapley, John (New York University).; Shear, T. Leslie.; John V. Sheehan & Co.; Sheldon, A. E. (Nebraska State Historical Society).; Shellenberger, Grace [Davenport (IA) Public Library].; Sheridan, Clare.; Shortridge, S. M.; Shrubbs, H. T. (Fitzwilliam Museum, Cambridge University).; Shuart, Louise (Curator, Washington’s HQ State Museum, NY).; Shultz, Norman.; Simmons, Joseph.; Sinclair, D. B.; Sinclair, Henry A.; Sinz, Walter A.; Sliepen, Ch.; Smith, David E. (Teachers College, Columbia University).; Smith, Elliott.; Smith, Fred S.; Smithsonian Institution.; Snoeck, M. W.; Snow, John H.
  - Box 2.6.3 #78 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Societa Numismatica Italiana.; Societe Francaise des Amis de la Medaille.; Societe Royale de Numismatique (Brussels, Belgium).; Societe Suisse de Numismatique (Geneva, Switzerland).; Society of Economic Geologists.; The Society of Medallists.; Society for the Promotion of Hellenic Studies.; Soderstrom, Alfred (Swedish Historical Society of America).; Sons of the Revolution of New York.; Sotheby, Wilkinson & Hodge.; Soutzo, Michel (Prince, Romania).; Sorensen, M.; South Manchuria Railway Co.; Special Libraries Association.; Spencer, Dwight.; Spencer-Churchill, E. J.; Speyer, James.; Spicer-Simson, T.; Spink & Son, Ltd.; Spink, Edwin (Spink & Son, Ltd.).; Spinazola, ________ (Director, Museo Nazionale, Naples).; Sponzel, J. (Staatliches Muenzkabinett, Dresden).; Springsted & Adamson.;; 2.6.4 #79;; Stafford, Morgan.; Starr, Charles S.; Starr, Louis M.; Stearns, Foster.; Stebbins, Eunice B.; G. E. Stechert Co.; E. Steiger & Co., booksellers.; Stephenson, Charles W.; Stevens, Edward F. (Librarian, Pratt Institute).; Stevens, Harry E.; Stevens, Leo E.; Stevenson, E. L.; W. K. Stewart Co.; Stewart, W. A. W. (Seawanhaka Corinthian Yacht Club).; Stewart, William Rhinelander.; Stewart Weir.; Stickney, Albert (Jr.).; Stikeman & Co., bookbinders.; Stillemans, _______ (Msgr.).; Stillman, C. C.; F. W. Stillman Co.; Stimmel Brothers.; Stonborough, J.; Stone, Charles G. (Connecticut Society, Sons of the Revolution).; Stone, Edmund J.; Stone, W. C. (Springfield Public Library).; Storer, Malcolm.; Stow, Charles (Editor, Christian Science Monitor).; A. Stowell & Co.; Stowell, J. W.; Stowell, Ruth.; Strauss, Harry.; Strena Buliciana.; Strohn, Adam (Librarian, Detroit Public Library).; Strumer, Samuel.; Strunz, William F.; Sturgio, F. K.; Sulgrane Institution.; Sullivan, Cornelius J.; Sullivan George H.; The Surney.; Sutton, George W. (Jr.).; Svoronos, A. (Le Musee National de Numismatique, Athens).; Svoronos, Jean N. (Director, National Numismatic Museum, Athens).; Swanson, Jonathan M.; Swasey, Ambrose.; Swedish Mint (Stockholm, Sweden).; Swedish Numismatic Society.; Swem, E. C.; Swets & Zeitlinger.; Sykes, G. E.; Sykes, P.
  - Box 2.6.5 #80 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Content
    T (unsorted).
  - Box 2.6.6 #81 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Tack, Augustus V.; Taft, Henry W.; Tanzer, Helen H.; Tapley, Henry F.; D. B. Taraporevala Sons & Co.; Tatman, Charles T.; Taylor, Robert L.; Teall, Gardner.; Ten Eyck, James.; Tenney, Edward.; Thal, Carl (Curator, Milwaukee Public Museum).; Thalheimer, Sidney.; Thebaud, Paul G.; Thom, Robert W.; Thomas, Charles G. M.; Thomas R.; Thompson & Norris Co.; Thompson, Albert W.; Thompson, Frederick (Mrs.).; Thompson, John H.; Thompson, W. Gilman.; Thompson, Grace [Librarian, East Orange (NJ) Public Library].; Thorne, W. J.; Thorndike, A. H.; Thorson, Nelson.; Thresher, E. S.; Thurston, R. C. Ballard.; Tice & Lynch.; Tiernann, Bernard.; Tilden, George L.; Tiffany & Co.; Tilden & Thurber.; Tilney, J. S.; Toplitz, Robert L.; Torrey, Charles C.; Torrey, Fred M.; Tourneur, Victor (Societe Royale Numismatic, Brussels, Belgium).; Tracy, Louis.; Treal, C. W.; Treat, Robert W.; Tremblay, P. O.; Triebel, F. E.; Triggs, A. B.; Towbridge, Alfred P.; Tsangaris, V. C.; Tuck, Edward.; Tucker, Lauri (Bibliothek das Universitas, Helsinki, Finland).; Tuthill, Luther B. Box 2.6.7 #82 U (unsorted).; Underhill, Adelaide (Librarian, Vassar College Library).; Underwood, Oscar (U.S. House of Representatives).; United States—Copyright Office.; United States—Customs Office.; United States—Government Printing Office.; United States—Commerce and Labor, Department of.; United States—Interior, Department of.; United States—State, Department of.; United States—Treasury, Department of.; United States—Treasury, Department of—Mint.; United States—Navy, Secretary of.; University of California at Berkeley.; University of Chicago.; University of Cincinnati.; University of Glasgow.; University of Illinois.; University of Kansas.; University of Pennsylvania.; University of Padau.; University of Wisconsin.; Unz & Co., 1912.; Unz & Co., 1913.; Unz & Co., 1914.; Unz & Co., 1915.; Unz & Co., 1916-1918.
  - Box 2.7.1 #83 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    V (unsorted).; Vail, A. W.; Vail, William.; Valentine, David W.; Valentine, G.; Valentine, W. H.; Van Amringe, Guy.; Van Brunt, A.; Van Buren, A. W. (Librarian, American Academy in Rome).; Van Deusen, Albert H.; Van Deventer, H. B. (Mrs.); G. Broes Van Dort Company.; Van Dyke, John C.; van Kerkwyk, A. O. (Director, Royal Coin Cabinet, The Hague, Holland).; Van Norden, Warner.; Van Nappen, R.; D. Van Nostrand Co.; Van Rensselaer, Schuyler (Mrs.).; Van Seebeck, Maurice.; Van Trappen, Raoul.; Van Voast, Horace.; Van Wert, William.; Van Winkle, ________.; Vanderbilt, Cornelius.; Vanderbilt, William K.; Vanderbilt, William K. (Mrs.).; Vanderlip, Frank A.; Vaupel, William.; Verlag des Boersenvereins der Deutschen Buchhaendler zu Leipzig.; Vernon, Frederic.; Vernon, Paul E.; Verplanck, William E.; Victor Emanuel (King, Italy).; Vicenzi, C. (Director, Soc. Numismatica Italiana).; Villalon, Jose R.; Villard, A. E.; Ville, Q. B.; Vincent, George A.; Vingaprova, Raymond.; The Vitagraph Company.; Viti, Marcel A.; Vitry, G.; Voetter, Thomas W.; Vogelsang, Philip.; von Bahrfeldt, Max; von Zambaur, Eduard.; Voynow, Edward B.; Voss, Reuben T.; Vreeland, N.
  - Box 2.7.2 #84 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    W (unsorted).
  - Box 2.7.3 #85 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Wade, J. H.; Wadepuhl, Otto.; Wadley & Smythe.; Wadlin, H. (Boston Public Library).; Wainwright, J. M.; Waitt, Joseph E.; Wakeman, A.; Walker, A. Stanley (College of Wooster, Wooster, Ohio).; Walker & Chambers.; Walker, William J.; Wall, Alexander J. (Librarian, New York Historical Society).; Walroth, H. A. (Director, Royal Mint, Stockholm, Sweden)..; Walsh, Joseph.; Walters, Henry.; Wanamaker, Rodman (NYC Mayor’s Committee for the Reception of Distinguished Visitors), 1919.; Warburton, Thomas.; Warburg, Felix M.; Ward, Frank B.; Warner and Swasey Co.; Warner, William E.; Warner Olin L.; Warren, Richard F.; Warren, Whitney.; Warnshuis, A. L. (National Missionary Conference, Shanghai), 1913.; Waterbury, John I.; Wayte, William.; Webb, Grace.; Watrous, Harry W.; Watson, Sue E.; Waverly Press.; Way, James.
  - Box 2.7.4 #86 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Weber, Shirley H. (Princeton University).; Weeks, William R.; Weeks, William R. (Mrs.).; Wehn, James A.; Weight, E. M.; Weil, Henri.; Weinert, Albert.; Weinman, A. A.; Weissbach, F. H. (Universitats-Bibliothek Leipzig).; Welch, William M.; Welcher, Emma Parke Avery.; Wendt, Julia B.; West, Allen B. (University of Cincinnati).; West, Allen B.; Westermann, W. L. (Columbia University).; Westervelt, Leonidas.; Westhorpe, Arthur W.; Westinghouse, H.; Wetmore, William. Box 2.7.5 #87 White, Herbert (CT Society of the Sons of the American Revolution).; White, Hugh W. (American Presbyterian Mission, China).; White John J.; Whitehead & Hoag Co.; Whitehead, R. B.; Whiting, Frederick.; Whiting, Giles.; Whitney, Caspar.; Whittemore, Thomas.; Whiton, John M.; Wickes, John Y.; Wicks, William R.; Wild, Henry (Williams College).; Wiley, William A.; Wilharm, G. T. E.; Wilkin, Joseph M.; Willey, W. L.; Williams, Alice.; Williams, D.; Williams, E. M. (Mrs.).; Williams, Harry F.; Williams, John.; Williams, Linsley (National Tuberculor Association).; Williams R. H.; Williams, A. C. (Medal Clerk, U.S. Mint, Philadelphia).; Williamson, W.; Wilmerding, Julia.; H. W. Wilson Co.; Wilson, W. W. C.; Wilson, Barker and Wager (Spring probate).; Winans, Charles S. (U.S. Consul, Czechoslovakia).; Wingate, George W. (Victory Hall Association).; Winship, Addison L.; Winter, Ezra.; Winthrop, Grenville L.; Wisconsin State Historical Society.; Wisconsin State Normal School.
  - Box 2.7.6 #88 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Wolcott, H. R.; Wolf, Estelle (Ms.).; Wood, Howland.; Wood, Howland—death of.; Wood, Richard D.; Wood, Walter.; Wood, William C.; Woodbridge, Freeman.; Woodbury, C. J. H.; Woodbury, John C.; Woodhull, Oliver J. (Mrs.).; Woodin, William H.; Woodward, A. M. Tracey.; Woolsey, L. J.; Woolverton, William H.; Worchester (MA) Art Museum.; Worchester, Edwin D.; Work, Eunice (Wheaton College).; World Metric Standardization Council.; Wormser, Moritz.; Wormser, Moritz (Mrs.).; Worthen, T. W. D.
  - Box 2.7.7 #89 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Wray, Henry Russell.; Wright, E. E.; Wright, H. Nelson.; Wright, Rebecca (Vermont Historical Society).; Wulfing, John Max.; Wurtzbach, Carl.; Wykes, Hunter (Pilgrims Society of the United States).; Wyckoff, Edward G.; Wyckoff, Peter B.; Wyman, Arthur C.; Wymer, W. G.; Wyman, Walter C.
  - Box 2.8.1 #90 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    Yale University.; Yale University Press.; Yawger, H. H. (American Numismatic Association).; Yen, U. Y.; Yoder, Albert H.; York, Edward P.; Yosemite Museum.; Young, A. C.; Young, Mahonri.; Young, William E.; Younglove, Florence L.; Z (unsorted).; Zabala, Romulo (Museo Bartolomeo Mitre, Buenos Aires).; Zabriskie, Andrew C. (Mrs.).; Zabriskie, Christian A.; Zabriskie, George A.; Zamora, Crispulo.; Zantal, Ladislas E.; Zerbe, Farran.; Zettler, Emil R.; Zimmerman, Jeremiah (Syracuse University).; Zink, ____ (Bundessammlung von Medaillen, Muenzen und Geldzeichen, Vienna).; Zograph, Alexander (The Hermitage).; Zonaras, Cleanthis.
  - Box 2.8.21(1932)
    A.; B.; Baldwin, A. H.; Baer (Joseph) & Co.; C.; Cammann, George (Mrs.); Cox, Dorothy.; D.; E.; Eidlitz, Robert J.; F.; G.
  - Box 2.8.32 (1932)
    H.; Huntington Free Library and Reading Room.; I.; J.; K.; L.; Libraries.; M.; Medallic Art Company.; N.;; Box 2.8.43 (1932);; O.; P.; Q.; R.; S.; T.; U.; V.; W.; Work, Eunice.; Wormser, Moritz.
  - Box 2.8.62 (1933)
    A.; Applications for positions.; Andrews E. P.; B.; Baer (Joseph) and Company.; Baldwin (A.H.) and Son.; Banta Publishing Company.; Bellinger, Alfred.; C.; Cammann, George P. (Mrs.).; Council.; Cox, Dorothy
  - Box 3.1.13 (1933)
    I.; Intelligencer Printing Company.; J.; K.; L.; Libraries.; M.; Medallic Art Company.; Moser, Arthur H.; N.; National District Telegraph Company.; Newell, Edward T.; O.; P.; Pond, Shepard.; Pradeau, A. F.; Q.; R.; Regling, Kurt (Kaiser Friedrich Museum).; Robinson, E. P.
  - Box 3.1.24 (1933)
    S.; Seaby (B.A.), Ltd.; Spink and Son.; T.; Tuttle, Morehouse & Taylor Company.; V.; U.; W.; Waverly Press.; Weber, Shirley H.; West, Allan B.; Work, Eunice.; Wormser, Moritz.; Y-Z.
  - Box 3.1.31 (1934)
    A.; American District Telegraph Company.; B.; Baldwin (A.H.) and Son, Ltd.; Banta Publishing Company.; Bellinger, Alfred R.
  - Box 3.1.42 (1934)
    C.; Cammann, George P. (Mrs.).; Central Hanover Bank.; Council.; Cox, Dorothy.; D.; Drowne, Henry Russell.; Duffield, Frankfurter.; E.; F.; G.; Gillingham, Harrold E.
  - Box 3.1.53 (1934)
    H.; Harlem Printing Company.; Hispanic Society of America.; Huntington, Archer M.; I.; Intelligencer Press.; J.; K.; L.; Lancaster Press.; Libraries.; M.; Medallic Art Company.; N.; Newell, Edward T.; Nussbaum, Hans.; O.; P.; Pond, Shepard.; Pradeau, A. F.; Q.;; Box 3.1.6 (1934);; R.; Ravel, O.; Raymond, Wayte.; Regling, Kurt (Kaiser Friedrich Museum).; Robinson, E. P.; S.; Spink and Son, Ltd.; T.; U.; V.; van Kerkwijk, A O.; W.; Waverly Press.; Weber, Shirley H.; Work, Eunice.; Wormser, Moritz.; Y-Z.
  - Box 3.1.71 (1935)
    A.; Applications for employment.; B.; Baldwin (A.H.) & Son.; Banta Publishing Company.; C.; Cammann, George P. (Mrs.).; Central Hanover Bank.; Coach, Eunice Burr.; Council memoranda.
  - Box 3.2.12 (1935)
    D.; Duffield, Frankfurter.; E.; Eidlitz, Robert J.; F.; G.; Gillingham, Harrold.
  - Box 3.2.23 (1935)
    H.; Hildreth Printing Company.; Hirsch, Jacob.; Hispanic Society of America.; Huntington Library and Reading Room.; I.; Intelligencer Printing Company.; J.; K.; L.; Lancaster Press.; Libraries.
  - Box 3.2.34 (1935)
    M.; Medallic Art Company.; Moser, Arthur H.; N.; O.; P.; Pond, Shepard.; Pradeau, A. H.; Quartich (Bernard), Ltd.; R.; Ravel, O.; Raymond, Wayte.; Regling, Kurt (Kaiser Friedrich Museum).; Robinson, E. S. G. (British Museum)
  - Box 3.2.45 (1935)
    S; Scoville, Herbert.; B.A. Seaby, Ltd.; Spink and Son, Ltd.; T; U.; Vlasto, Michel P.; W; Waverly Press.; Weber, Shirley H.; Work, Eunice.; Wormser, Moritz.; Y-Z.
  - Box 3.2.51 (1936)
    A.; Annamite gold coins.; Applications for employment.; Acknowledgements.; B.; Baldwin (A.H.) & Sons, Ltd.; Bellinger, Alfred R.; British Numismatic Society.; Bullowa, David M.; C.; Cammann, Jean B.; Central Hanover Bank.; Clement, Paul.; Council memoranda.; D.; E.; Eidlitz, Robert J.; Elder, Thomas.
  - Box 3.2.62 (1936)
    F.; G.; Gillingham, Harrrold E.; H.; Hispanic Society of America.; Huntington, Archer M.; Intelligencer Printing Company.; Ives, Herbert E.; K.; L.; Libraries.; M.; Medals.; Moser, Arthur H.;; Box 3.3.13 (1936);; N.; New England Preparatory Schools.; Nussbaum, Hans. O.; P.; Personal.; Quaritch (Bernard), Ltd.; R.; Raymond, Wayte.; Robinson, E. S. G. (British Museum).; S.; Santamaria, P Smith, Elliott.; Spink & Son, Ltd.
  - Box 3.3.24 (1936)
    T.; Universities.; W.; Waverly Press.; Westbrook Publishing Company.; Work, Eunice.; Wormser, Moritz.
  - Box 3.3.31 (1937
    A.; American Council of Learned Societies.; B.; Bookbinders.; Brunner will.; C.; Cahn, Herbert A.; Cammann, Jean.; Commission International de Numismatique.; Council memoranda.; D.; Duffield, Frankfurter.; E.; Eidlitz (Marc) & Son, Inc.
  - Box 3.3.42 (1937)
    F.; Forms.; G.; Gallatin, Albert.; Gillingham, Harrold E.; H.; I.; Intelligencer Printing Co.; Ives,
  - Box 3.3.53 (1937)
    O.; P.; Publications Committee.; Q.; R.; S.; Spink & Son, Ltd.; T.; U.; V.; W.; Wormser, Moritz.
  - Box 3.3.61 (1938)
    A.; American Council of Learned Societies.; Bellinger, Alfred R.; British Museum.
  - Box 3.3.72 (1938)
    C.; Central Hanover Bank.; Clapp, George H.; Council memoranda.; D.; Duffield, Frankfurter G.; E.
  - Box 3.4.13 (1938)
    F.; Fecht, A. J.; G.; Gillingham, Harrold E.; H.; Hildreth, E. L.; I.; Ives, Herbert E.
  - Box 3.4.24 (1938)
    J.; K.; L.; Laferta.; Libraries.; M.; Mc.; Medallic Art Co.; Meriden Gravure Co.; N.; O.
  - Box 3.4.35 (1938)
    P.; Personnel.; Publicity.; Q.; R.
  - Box 3.4.46 (1938)
    S.; S.; T.; Taylor.; U.; V.; W.
  - Box 3.4.51 (1939)
    A.; American Council of Learned Societies.; American Council of Learned Societies.; B.
  - Box 3.4.62 (1939)
    C.; Central Hanover Bank.; D.; E.; F.
  - Box 3.4.73 (1939)
    G.; G.; Gillingham, Harrold E.; H.; I.; J.
  - Box 3.5.14 (1939)
    K.; L.; M.; Mc.; Milbank, Samuel R.
  - Box 3.5.25 (1939)
    N.; O.; P.; Q.; R.; Raymond, Wayte.
  - Box 3.5.36 (1939)
    S.; Spink & Son.; T.
  - Box 3.5.47 (1939)
    U.; V.; World’s Fair.; X-Z.
  - Box 9.7.1 A-B (1940)
    A. Addressograph stencils.; American Council of Learned Societies.; American District Telegraph Company.; Applicants.; B.
  - Box 9.7.2 C-N (1940)
    Central Hanover.; D.; E.; F.; Gillingham.; Gift acknowledgements.; G.; H.; J.; K.; L.; Milbank, Samuel.; Mc/Mac.; M.; May, E.W.; N.; Noe, Sydney P.
  - Box 9.7.3 O-Z (1940)
    O. P. Pond, Shepard.; Publicity.; R.; S.; U.; Arrow Service.; T.; Sales Tax.; Spink.; V.; W.; X-Z.
  - Box 9.8.1 A-K (1941)
    A.; B.; American Council of Learned Societies.; American District Telegraph Company.; Addressograph.; Applicants.; Central Hanover.; Council.; D.; E.; F.; Gift acknowledgements.; Gillingham.; G.; Hospital.; H.; I.; J.; K.
  - Box 9.8.2 L-Z (1941)
    L.; Mc/Mac.; Milbank, Samuel.; M.; Newell, E.T.; Noe, Sydney.; Numismatic Notes and Monographs/Numismatic Studies.; N.; P.; Pond, Shepard.; Robinson collection.; Q.; Spink.; T.; U.; V.; Wants.; X-Z.
  - Box 9.9.1 A-I (1942)